[
  {"question": "فرنسا", "answer": "باريس"},
  {"question": "اليابان", "answer": "طوكيو"},
  {"question": "مصر", "answer": "القاهرة"},
  {"question": "روسيا", "answer": "موسكو"},
  {"question": "ألمانيا", "answer": "برلين"},
  {"question": "إيطاليا", "answer": "روما"},
  {"question": "المملكة المتحدة", "answer": "لندن"},
  {"question": "إسبانيا", "answer": "مدريد"},
  {"question": "الولايات المتحدة", "answer": "واشنطن"},
  {"question": "كندا", "answer": "أوتاوا"}
]
